clarityelections.com 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy - SOE a Scytl company

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

## How do we use your information?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
  * To improve our Web site  
(We continually strive to improve our Web site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve customer service  
(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect others or our rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Web site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the modification date below. This policy was last modified on August 11, 2010.

## Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

SOE Software Corporation

http://www.soesoftware.com

5426 Bay Center Drive  
Tampa, FL 33609  
soesupport@soesoftware.com  
(813) 490-7150
